<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="151747" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Signature Logistics" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Keep signature factories productive with configurable vehicles, storage, restocking, and clearer delivery information." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
Signature factories can stop producing when their small vehicle fleet, limited storage, or missing input materials create a logistics bottleneck. Signature Logistics gives you direct control over those limits so these unique buildings can spend more time producing and less time waiting.

WHAT YOU CAN CONTROL

- Maximum delivery vehicles: 1-100, default 20.
- Storage capacity: 10-5,000 tonnes, default 500 tonnes.
- Input restock target: 25-100%, default 25%.
- Separate vehicle and storage limits for each signature factory.
- One-click reset from a building override back to your global defaults.

Open Options &gt; Signature Logistics to set the defaults used by every signature factory. To customize one building, select it and use the Signature building limits controls shown immediately above Vehicles in use. Your global settings save across game restarts, while building overrides save with the city.

SMARTER RESTOCKING

The mod checks required production inputs and can request more materials before the factory runs dry. Purchases still use the game's normal economy: real local suppliers or outside connections, normal costs, actual delivery vehicles, and a working road route are all required. Resources are never teleported or created for free.

BETTER DELIVERY INFORMATION

Expand Vehicles in use to see each delivery vehicle's current cargo, capacity, and approximate distance to its destination on one row. The original vehicle status link remains clickable.

SCOPE

Only signature-building companies are changed. Ordinary zoned industry, service vehicles, cargo stations, and unrelated buildings keep their normal behavior.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail-signature-logistics.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/vehicle-details.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/global-settings.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/building-logistics.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/building-overrides.png" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.2" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.0*" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="Fixed per-building vehicle and storage controls not appearing for signature factories. The controls now resolve the selected factory correctly, render once in a compact native panel, save custom limits, and provide a clear Use global reset action." />
	<!--<ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog>-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Meapy/signature-logistics" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
