<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="151747" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Signature Logistics" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Stabilize signature factories with configurable logistics, dependable full-load imports, stronger starting stock, and clearer deliveries." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
Signature factories can stop producing when their small vehicle fleet, limited storage, or missing input materials create a logistics bottleneck. Signature Logistics gives you direct control over those limits so these unique buildings can spend more time producing and less time waiting.

WHAT YOU CAN CONTROL

- Maximum delivery vehicles: 1-100, default 20.
- Storage capacity: 10-5,000 tonnes, default 500 tonnes.
- Input restock target: 25-100%, default 25%.
- Separate vehicle and storage limits for each signature factory.
- One-click reset from a building override back to your global defaults.

Open Options &gt; Signature Logistics to set the defaults used by every signature factory. To customize one building, select it and use the Building logistics controls shown immediately above Vehicles in use. Your global settings save across game restarts, while building overrides save with the city.

MORE STABLE COMPANIES

The game can use the same internal move-away marker for genuine bankruptcy and random tax or worker-shortage churn. Signature Logistics preserves a signature tenant through the random churn path while still allowing genuine bankruptcy after the company's total worth stays below the game's threshold for the full grace period.

Priority restocking also checks the company's exact game-calculated worth before ordering. The mod pauses its extra purchase when that truckload would consume the remaining bankruptcy cushion; normal production, selling, and the game's own economy continue.

MORE STARTING RESOURCES

Each newly observed signature tenant receives a second copy of its positive non-money starting resources. Typical industrial inputs increase from 15 tonnes to 30 tonnes each, commercial inputs from 3 tonnes to 6 tonnes each, and eligible 1-tonne output or extractor stock to 2 tonnes. The company's bank balance is unchanged, and saved tenant history prevents the grant from repeating after save/reload. Existing cities may grant the current tenant this one-time boost when first loaded with this version.

WHY THE PREVIOUS COMPANY LEFT

The Company section records the previous signature tenant's departure reason and saves it with the city. It can report bankruptcy with missing materials, no customers, educated-worker shortage, general worker shortage, or other losses; rent/property relocation; and an explicit external/load replacement fallback when the game leaves no reliable cause.

SMARTER RESTOCKING

The mod compares required inputs by recipe-weighted production coverage, including materials in storage, pending purchases, and cargo already inbound. Empty outbound buying trucks reserve their full capacity until they load, preventing repeated orders against the same apparent deficit. It prioritizes the material that will stop production first, then requests a full largest-compatible truck whenever storage and the company's bankruptcy cushion allow it. If a full load will not fit, the request can fall back to 75% capacity; smaller priority orders wait instead of intentionally dispatching nearly empty trucks.

Supplemental priority restocking uses outside connections for dependable stock and still pays normal import costs, uses real delivery vehicles, follows the native pathfinder, and requires working road routes. Resources are never teleported or created for free. The game's ordinary company purchases remain unchanged and can still buy from local suppliers.

BETTER DELIVERY INFORMATION

Expand Vehicles in use to see each delivery vehicle's current cargo, capacity, and approximate distance to its destination on one row. The original vehicle status link remains clickable.

SCOPE

Only signature-building companies are changed. Ordinary zoned industry, service vehicles, cargo stations, and unrelated buildings keep their normal behavior.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail-signature-logistics.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/vehicle-details.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/global-settings.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/building-logistics.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/building-overrides.png" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.6" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.0*" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="Fixed repeated low-load buying. Empty outbound buying trucks now reserve their full capacity, preventing the same deficit from spawning a new request every 64 ticks. Supplemental priority restocking now uses outside connections for dependable full loads, while the game's ordinary local company purchases remain unchanged." />
	<!--<ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog>-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Meapy/signature-logistics" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
